# VERONICA BERGSTRÖM

### Front End Developer

+46725397833 • frontend.veronica@gmail.com • https://www.linkedin.com/in/veronica-b-a863b567/

• https://github.com/innoVeraz • Stockholm

#### Skills

React · CI/CD · Crm · Css · Docker · E2E · Figma · FlexBox · Git · Github · Html · Html5 · Javascript · Jira · Next.js · NoSql · Photoshop · Postgres · Redux · Sass · Socket.io · Sql · Tailwind · Typescript · VS Code · Vue · Agile · GraphQL · Jest · Cypress · Unit testing

### Experience

Oneflow AB Stockholm

Front End Developer 10/2023 - 05/2024

- · React, Redux and Sass
- · Became TypeScript Pioneer
- Migrated components from flow to TypeScript
- · Helped implement updated Subscription & Billing page with self-upgrade feature
- · Built reusable components
- Bug solving and refactoring class components to functional
- · Ticket management in Jira, Version control with Git and Atlassian Bamboo for CI/CD
- SaaS product

Afound Stockholm

Customer Success Manager

08/2016 - 09/2019

- · Start up, project management
- · Built B2B and B2C department
- · Created work processes and system requirements for CRM.
- · Recruited and trained new employees and business partners.
- Built documentation and managed onboarding for new colleagues and business partners.

Fyndig AB Stockholm

Flow Manager 08/2012 - 04/2016

- · Start up, project management
- · Defined system requirements for development and testing.
- · Onboarding in CRM and other systems.
- · Recruitment B2B support
- · Delegated daily prioritized tasks
- Managed escalated issues from B2C

Support Payzone Stockholm

Office Manager 12/2010 - 09/2012

- Daily management of office spaces and reception.
- · Planned internal events and managed office supplies.
- · Assisted the finance department with administrative tasks.
- · Technical support.

### Training / Courses

Math — NTI School 2020

Business Economics — Astar 2021

Web development — Astar 2021

### Education

Stockholm Medieinstitutet AB

Front End Developer

- · JavaScript, TypeScript
- React, VUE3
- Testing (e2e, unit)
- HTML5, CSS (Sass, Tailwind, BEM, Grid, Flexbox)
- · Figma, Photoshop
- UX & Usability
- Work methodics for developers
- Agile working methods
- Prisma, Next.js, Docker, Redux, Zustand, Atlassian Bamboo
- · Fly.io, Socket.io, postgres, VS Code, Tailwind

#### About

"Veronica has shown many valuable traits as a developer. She is curious, thorough, and has great problem-solving skills. She wants to improve things and isn't afraid to question solutions. Veronica has also impressed me with her ability to work independently, far more than I initially expected. Socially, she has been a joy to work with. She is happy, social, and communicative, which has greatly contributed to a positive and collaborative work environment. She gets along well with everyone and has built strong relationships across different departments."

/Amanda Olsson Front End Developer and mentor, Oneflow AB

### Languages

English Proficient ●●●● Swedish Native ••••

## Find me online

Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/veroni ca-b-a863b567/

Github

https://github.com/innoVeraz

CV Enhancy

06/2024 - 06/2024